const questionArray = [
  {
  question: 'Who sponsored the 1992 Lithuanian Mens Basketball Team?',
  answers: ['FIBA', 'Ross Perot', 'The Grateful Dead'],
  correct: 'The Grateful Dead'
},
{
  question: 'Which team did Lithuania defeat to win the Bronze medal?',
  answers: ['Croatia', 'Unified Team (Former USSR)', 'Team USA'], 
  correct: 'Unified Team (Former USSR)'
},
{
question: 'What model car/s trunk can fit the 7 foot Arvydas Sabonis?',
answers: ['Cadillac', 'Lada', 'Volkswagen'],
correct: 'Cadillac'
},
{
  question:'The players used to purchase retail items like jeans and appliances in Europe and the US to resell for a profit back home. Which player was considered the best entrepenuer?',
  answers: ['Valdemaras Chomicius', 'Arvydas Sabonis', 'Sarunas Marciulionis'],
  correct: 'Valdemaras Chomicius'
},
{
  question: 'Which documentary covered the team in the 1992 Olympics?',
  answers: ['The Other Dream Team', 'The Dream Team', 'Space Jam'],
  correct: 'The Other Dream Team'
},
{
  question: 'Who played for the Portland Trailblazers from 1995-2003?',
  answers: ['Sarunas Maciulionis', 'Rimas Kurtinaitis', 'Arvydas Sabonis'],
  correct: 'Arvydas Sabonis'
},
{
  question: 'During the 1989 San Francisco earthquake, this player appeared at a commuter train accident in his Golden State Warriors warmup outfit pulling trapped passengers and administering first aid.',
  answers: ['Valdemaras Chomicius', 'Arturus Karnisovas', 'Sarunas Marciulionis'],
  correct: 'Sarunas Marciulionis'
},
{
  question: 'Half of the team was born in this city, and the city itself is home to BC Zalgiris, one of the oldest professional teams in the Euroleague. What city is this?',
  answers: ['Kaunas', 'Kretinga', 'Klaipeda'],
  correct: 'Kaunas'
},
{
  question: 'Rimas Kurtinaitis never played in the NBA, yet he did participate in the NBA, in what event?',
  answers: ['Coaching for the San Antonio Spurs', 'NBA All Star Weekend Dunk Contest', 'NBA All Star Weekend Three-Point Contest'],
  correct: 'NBA All Star Weekend Three-Point Contest'
},
{
  question: 'Who is Arvydas Sabonis favorite basketball player?',
  answers: ['Andrei Kirilenko', 'Shaquille ONeal', 'Larry Bird'],
  correct: 'Larry Bird'
}
];
